

CONTACT

(402) 429-9944 hello@haylikent.design

WEBSITE

haylikent.design

AWARDS

SCC Deans List October 2018-Present

AFFILIATIONS

AIGA Nebraska October 2018–Present

REFERENCES

Available upon request

CAREER SUMMARY

The Graphic Design Media Arts program at Southeast Community College has prepared me to start my own design journey. Through the combination of my education and my work experience, I have developed strong digital, print, and conceptual project planning skills that will be an asset in a future design position.

EDUCATION

A.A.S. in Graphic Design and Media Arts

Southeast Community College Lincoln, NE | Exp. Graduation Summer 2020

Core learning included: corporate identity and branding using Adobe Illustrator, web design and development with HTML5, CSS3, Invision, GitHub, Adobe Dreamweaver, and Visual Studio Code, package design with Adobe Dimension, Nikon D3400 photography—studio and environmental, post-production with Adobe Photoshop and Lightroom, interactive design in Adobe XD, and publication design in Adobe InDesign.

JOB EXPERIENCE

Graphic Design Intern

Infusionmedia, Lincoln, NE | January 2019-Present

Book design: including cover and innards using InDesign and Illustrator, ePublication using PressBooks, editing and saving photos and content for web use through Photoshop and Illustrator, worked collaboratively and independently, as well as remote, utilizing Toggl, Slack and Dropbox.

Freelance Graphic Designer

Lincoln, NE | January 2019-Present

Conceptualizing, client relations and communication, problem solving, identity, logo, and promotional item design.

Marketing Team Lead

Lincoln Escape Room, Lincoln, NE | March 2020-Present

Creating promotional graphics for multiple social media platforms, managing client inquiries, reporting to marketing director, collaboration with company leadership, maintaining customer service and keyholder duties.

Keyholder

Lincoln Escape Room, Lincoln, NE | November 2017-February 2020

Independently managed, performed opening and closing duties, managed groups from start to finish in their escape room experiences, created customer bookings online and over the phone, answered any customer questions, created and repaired props and puzzles for escape rooms, maintained clean public areas, and completed any other tasks upon management request.